[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What's going on at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, right now, what firefighters have done is they've sort of taken the upper hand at least on the northern flank of this fire.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "right", "now", ",", "what", "firefighters", "have", "done", "is", "they", "'ve", "sort", "of", "taken", "the", "upper", "hand", "at", "least", "on", "the", "northern", "flank", "of", "this", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "You stayed at your house all day, but when you left, did you think you were going to return to a house?", "question_tokens": ["You", "stayed", "at", "your", "house", "all", "day", ",", "but", "when", "you", "left", ",", "did", "you", "think", "you", "were", "going", "to", "return", "to", "a", "house", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "With the firemen giving me excellent odds that they had pretty good control of things at the time, the answer would be yes.", "answer_tokens": ["With", "the", "firemen", "giving", "me", "excellent", "odds", "that", "they", "had", "pretty", "good", "control", "of", "things", "at", "the", "time", ",", "the", "answer", "would", "be", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott Ochoa"]}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Can you spell your name please?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "spell", "your", "name", "please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Scott Ochoa, city manager, O-C-H-O-A.", "answer_tokens": ["Scott", "Ochoa", ",", "city", "manager", ",", "O-C-H-O-A", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kyung Lah"]}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Can you come back, sir?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "come", "back", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Let me go back to Kyung Lah now.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "go", "back", "to", "Kyung", "Lah", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Did you think that you were ever going to be returning to a home yesterday?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "that", "you", "were", "ever", "going", "to", "be", "returning", "to", "a", "home", "yesterday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "I mean, what kind of pit is that in your belly?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "pit", "is", "that", "in", "your", "belly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "It's devastating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "devastating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Anything you want to add, Paul?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "you", "want", "to", "add", ",", "Paul", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I feel very fortunate today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "very", "fortunate", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Syria", "U.S.", "Syria"]}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "What is likely to be the White House reaction to what's happened here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "likely", "to", "be", "the", "White", "House", "reaction", "to", "what", "'s", "happened", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Well, nobody's talking about it publicly, you know, but President Obama is literally getting asked about Syria every day, and again today, with this ratcheting up of tensions, the president once again said you know, no prospect that he can see of putting U.S. ground troops into Syria.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "nobody", "'s", "talking", "about", "it", "publicly", ",", "you", "know", ",", "but", "President", "Obama", "is", "literally", "getting", "asked", "about", "Syria", "every", "day", ",", "and", "again", "today", ",", "with", "this", "ratcheting", "up", "of", "tensions", ",", "the", "president", "once", "again", "said", "you", "know", ",", "no", "prospect", "that", "he", "can", "see", "of", "putting", "U.S.", "ground", "troops", "into", "Syria", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "And is it -- is the fear, Barbara, that the Syrians may respond in kind now against Israel?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "--", "is", "the", "fear", ",", "Barbara", ",", "that", "the", "Syrians", "may", "respond", "in", "kind", "now", "against", "Israel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, I think that the Israelis and all the countries in the region certainly would be prepared for that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "Israelis", "and", "all", "the", "countries", "in", "the", "region", "certainly", "would", "be", "prepared", "for", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "This will be national news.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "will", "be", "national", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "DT", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Is this brand terminally damaging?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "brand", "terminally", "damaging", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "No, because she did what some are calling the apology tour.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "she", "did", "what", "some", "are", "calling", "the", "apology", "tour", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Arrested for what?", "question_tokens": ["Arrested", "for", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "DUI.", "answer_tokens": ["DUI", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What did I get arrested for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "I", "get", "arrested", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "You wouldn't listen to what he said to do and you kept getting out of the car.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "listen", "to", "what", "he", "said", "to", "do", "and", "you", "kept", "getting", "out", "of", "the", "car", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Janice?", "question_tokens": ["Janice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, I mean, remember, she has been one of the biggest actresses in Hollywood since her early 20s.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "remember", ",", "she", "has", "been", "one", "of", "the", "biggest", "actresses", "in", "Hollywood", "since", "her", "early", "20s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "So it's a very unique, interesting combination, you know what I mean?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "unique", ",", "interesting", "combination", ",", "you", "know", "what", "I", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "It's a smash hit around the world and you get zero dollars?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "smash", "hit", "around", "the", "world", "and", "you", "get", "zero", "dollars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Well, I didn't ask for anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "ask", "for", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "What about the people like me that can neither write none of this nor dance?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "the", "people", "like", "me", "that", "can", "neither", "write", "none", "of", "this", "nor", "dance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "MD", "DT", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "But you can listen, you can whistle.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "you", "can", "listen", ",", "you", "can", "whistle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "The greatest guitarist in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "greatest", "guitarist", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "How do you cope with that title?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "cope", "with", "that", "title", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I didn't come up with the title.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "come", "up", "with", "the", "title", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Well, talking of Brad Paisley, this furor that erupted over \"Accidental Racist\", what were you trying to achieve?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "talking", "of", "Brad", "Paisley", ",", "this", "furor", "that", "erupted", "over", "``", "Accidental", "Racist", "''", ",", "what", "were", "you", "trying", "to", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "What I was trying to achieve is --", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "was", "trying", "to", "achieve", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad Paisley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "You know, I hope -- you get what I'm saying?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "hope", "--", "you", "get", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "On top of that, there's plenty of white people that don't like me.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "top", "of", "that", ",", "there", "'s", "plenty", "of", "white", "people", "that", "do", "n't", "like", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Love conquers all, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Love", "conquers", "all", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "And music, too.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "music", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "CC", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "What is the art of survival?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "art", "of", "survival", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Good genes and -- no, actually, just music.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "genes", "and", "--", "no", ",", "actually", ",", "just", "music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Could you still do that \"Jump\"?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "still", "do", "that", "``", "Jump", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Same height?", "question_tokens": ["Same", "height", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Hurts a little more when I land.", "answer_tokens": ["Hurts", "a", "little", "more", "when", "I", "land", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "How do you get details for that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "details", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Go to llcoolj.com.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "to", "llcoolj.com", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you holding up OK?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "holding", "up", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "I'm doing well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "What do you think is really going on now at the \"Today\" show?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "really", "going", "on", "now", "at", "the", "``", "Today", "''", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I think the \"Today\" show is in comeback mode, just as it should be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "``", "Today", "''", "show", "is", "in", "comeback", "mode", ",", "just", "as", "it", "should", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt", "Jay Leno"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Have they known each other well, do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "known", "each", "other", "well", ",", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Well, we heard Matt last night mentioned to Jay Leno that they talked sometime about each other's shows.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "heard", "Matt", "last", "night", "mentioned", "to", "Jay", "Leno", "that", "they", "talked", "sometime", "about", "each", "other", "'s", "shows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "That if you're right there at the top, you're going to get gunned down?", "question_tokens": ["That", "if", "you", "'re", "right", "there", "at", "the", "top", ",", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "get", "gunned", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "There's a lot to that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "lot", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "If you had been running NBC, would you have fired Ann Curry when they did?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "been", "running", "NBC", ",", "would", "you", "have", "fired", "Ann", "Curry", "when", "they", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "I'd like -- well, of course, I don't get paid nearly enough to answer this question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "like", "--", "well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "get", "paid", "nearly", "enough", "to", "answer", "this", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"], "PERSON": ["Ann Curry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Carr"]}, "docId": "130503pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Were you right to be dissing out a few stones into glass houses, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "right", "to", "be", "dissing", "out", "a", "few", "stones", "into", "glass", "houses", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "I thought David Carr's column was right on.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "David", "Carr", "'s", "column", "was", "right", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]